

### Contact

### **Phone**

+36 30 782 15 83

#### Email

dev.lukacs@gmail.com

### **Portfolio-site**

Click to redirect

### Pécs, Hungary

Ready to work remotely

## **Education**

Mate Academy | Coding Bootcamp
FRONTEND DEVELOPER

2022 – 2023

# **Expertise**

- Typescript, JavaScript (ES2015 2019)
- React, Next.js
- HTML5, CSS3, Sass (SCSS), BEM, Tailwind, Bulma
- Git/Github, VS Code, Chrome
   Developer Tools (incl. React), NPM
- Algorithms: Solved 200+ algorithmic tasks

# Language

English: Upper-Intermediate

Hungarian: Native

# JANOS LUKACS

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

## **About Me**

Having spent over a decade honing my skills at the online poker tables, I discovered the thrilling world of programming and I haven't looked back since. Last year I dove headfirst into a bootcamp program and quickly fell in love with the challenge and creativity of building web applications. With a solid understanding of technologies like HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, TypeScript, Tailwind and SASS, I'm ready to bring my unique background and passion to your next project.

# Experience

### **2022 - 2023**

Mate Academy | International Coding Bootcamp

### FRONTEND DEVELOPER

- Full-time development from 9:00 to 18:00;
- Solved more than 300 tasks;
- Adherence to strict deadlines and code review by middle and senior developers;
- Practical skills in conducting code reviews.

### Summer 2023 - present

Independent Full-Time Coding and Learning

- Constantly improving, learning new technologies and developing my portfolio projects.
- Feel free to explore them on my GitHub page or;
- On my personal portfolio site: <u>URL</u>

### 2010 - 2022

Sponsored Online Poker Player

 Leveraging my experience as a highly skilled multitable online poker player, I have sharpened my analytical and strategic thinking abilities. I excel at analyzing complex data and visualizing it to gain a competitive advantage, while constantly making lightning-fast decisions in a high-pressure environment.